Contact

tye.ratliff@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/tyrell-ratliff-247a8ab4 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Critical Care ACLS

BLS

Languages

English

Tyrell Ratliff

Tyrell Ratliff MSN, RN, CCRN

Dallas/Fort Worth Area

Summary

Experienced Registered Nurse with a demonstrated history of working in the hospital & health care industry. Skilled in Medical-Surgical, Medication Administration, Pediatric Advanced Life Support (PALS), TNCC, and Intensive Care. Strong healthcare services professional with a Bachelor's degree focused in Registered Nursing/Registered Nurse from Tarleton State University.

Experience

Glen Rose Medical Center Assistant Chief Nursing Officer July 2018 - Present (1 year 11 months) Glen Rose, Texas

Texas Health Resources

7 years

Charge Nurse-ICU November 2015 - Present (4 years 7 months)

Preceptor

November 2015 - Present (4 years 7 months)

CCRN

April 2015 - Present (5 years 2 months)

Agency nurse for Central Staffing Organization in the THR system

Staff RN

2013 - Present (7 years)

Central Staffing Organization

I am part of Texas Health Resources internal float pool. I work Med Surg, Tele, and ICU floors.

John Peter Smith Hospital
RN II ICU
February 2012 - April 2015 (3 years 3 months)
Page 1 of 2

JPS Health Network Staff RN

February 2012 - March 2015 (3 years 2 months)

A 36 bed Intensive Care Unit at a Level 1 Trauma center located in the heart of Tarrant County. The patient population varies from the indigent population to the middle to upper class. Our ICU is not specialized into types or classes of patients, but is a mixture of patients consisting of varying level of traumas, diverse amount of surgeries, difficult medical cases, neuro patients, and cardio-thoracic (open heart) patients. This type of environment is very fast paced and provides a more versatile learning environment that requires nurses to expand their knowledge and become competent in understanding the multitude of different complications seen in our area.

Education

Grantham University
MSN, Nursing Administration · (2019)

Tarleton State University

Bachelor's degree, Registered Nursing/Registered Nurse · (2007 - 2011)

Glen Rose High School High School Diploma · (2003 - 2007)